<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GMI Prospect Application</string>
    <string name="gapp_ov">Germany land of many opportunities, renowned for its technological achievements and the German higher education is one of the best in the world! A German university degree is highly respected by employers around the world and those from the Universities of Applied Science are very practice-oriented. \n\nFor these reasons, the German A-Level Preparatory Program (GAPP) was established at the German-Malaysian Institute in 2001 to prepare and qualify young Malaysians to further their study in the fields of engineering at the University of Applied Sciences which requires A Levels, TesfDAF and Vorpraktikum qualifications for enrolment.\n</string>
    <string name="gapp_subj">Students will undergo a 22-month preparatory programme at GMI, and also a 6-month intensive German Language training at various language centres in Germany before they are accepted for enrolment at the University of Applied Sciences (UAS).\n\n6-Month Programme at Language Centres in Germany\n• German Language from B2 - TestDAF\n• Intensive Intercultural and Study Skill Workshop\n• Advice on study placement\n• Technical German\n• Internship (depends on placement)</string>
    <string name="gufp_ov">GMI-UTP Foundation Programme (GUFP) is strategic partnership between GMI (German Malaysian Institute) and UTP (Universiti Teknologi PETRONAS). This programme is a one year foundation programme based on UTP foundation syllabus. Upon completion, students will be qualified to start their Undergraduate Programme at UTP.</string>
    <string name="gufp_subj"><![CDATA[Trimester 1\n• Chemistry I\n• Physics I\n• Mathematics I\n• Proficiency English\n\nTrimester 2\n• Thinking Skills\n• Islamic Studies / Moral Studies\n• Structured Algorithms & Programming\n• Technical English\n• Co-Curriculum\n\nTrimester 3\n• Physics II\n• Chemistry II\n• Mathematics II\n• Co-Curriculum\n]]></string>
    <string name="belt_ov">Collaboration program between GMI-UTeM are prepares graduates for careers in various electrical engineering disciplines. It combines theoretical, practical, and soft skill elements to develop well-rounded engineers. The program focuses on equipping students with the skills to meet industry needs through laboratory work, industrial training, design projects, and exposure to professional ethics and practice.\n\nThe BELT program at UTeM-GMI refers to the Bachelor of Electrical Engineering Technology with Honours program. The program code is BELT. This program is recognized by the MQA (Malaysian Qualifications Agency) and the accreditation body ETAC.</string>
    <string name="belt_subj">Focus on Industry Needs:\nThe program is designed to align with industry requirements, ensuring graduates are well-prepared for the workforce.\n\nBalanced Curriculum:\nIt integrates theoretical knowledge with practical application, including laboratory work, industrial training, and design projects.\n\nEmphasis on Professional Development:\nThe program incorporates elements of professional ethics, engineering practice, and exposure to industry through guest lectures, visits, and courses.</string>
    <string name="belt_path">Career Prospects:\nGraduates can find employment in various sectors, including semiconductor manufacturing, electrical component manufacturing, renewable energy, and automation systems.\n\nIn essence, the BELT program at UTeM aims to produce graduates who are not only technically competent but also possess the professional skills and ethical grounding to thrive in the dynamic field of electrical engineering technology.</string>
    <string name="eed1_path">1. Asisstant Mechatronics Engineer\n2. Automation Technical Specialist\n3. Automation System Designer\n4. Remote Operating Vehicle (ROV) Supervisor.\n</string>
    <string name="eed1_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Computer Programming\n• Electrical Principles\n• German Language 1\n• Pre-Calculus\n• Engineering Science\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Basic Metal Work\n• Technical Drawing & CAD\n\nSemester 2\n• Electronics\n• Technical English 1\n• German Language 2\n• Electronics Workshop\n• Calculus\n• Basic Turning & Milling\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban/ Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi 1\n\nSemester 3\n• Sensor & Transducer\n• Basic Engineering Metrology\n• Digital Systems\n• Technical English 2\n• Pneumatics & Hydraulics Technology\n• Machine Elements\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah/Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n• Community Services\n\nSemester 4\n• Electrical Machines & Control\n• Electrical Installation\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• Programmable Logic Controller\n• Machine Design\n• MEC Project Proposal\n• Industrial Management\n• Control Systems Application\n\nSemester 5\n• Industrial Robotics\n• Computer Integrated Manufacturing\n• MEC Final Project\n• Engineering Materials\n• Microcontroller\n• Power Electronics & Modern Drive Technology\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="eed1_ov">Mechatronics engineering technology is a unique synergistic integration of the three discipline areas namely mechanical engineering, electronics, and intelligent computer control to address the challenges of designing and deploying smart technologies. This unique multidisciplinary course offers you the opportunity to study the most exciting aspects of mechanical designs, electronics and control technology into the design and manufacture of intelligent systems. It is the cutting-edge of creating smarter products, devices and processes. Mechatronic components consider to be integrated in the industrial internet of things (IIoT) environment which is one of the keys enabling technologies for industry 4.0.</string>
    <string name="about_text">In 1991, German-Malaysian Institute (GMI), a hub for advanced skills training was established. GMI provides a comprehensive and well-balanced training of practical and theoretical. The institute offers a broad-based engineering education, with opportunities for specialization and self-directed learning and development.\n\n GMI offers diverse training programmes and services comprising full time diploma programmes, a pre-university programme (A-Level), skills upgrading technical courses, train-the-trainers programmes, and industrial consultancy and services.\n\n The birth of GMI was the outcome of a joint venture between the Governments of Malaysia and Germany. GMI is governed by a 10-member Board of Directors comprising representatives from both governments, plus public and industrial representatives. GMI had its first student enrollment in 1992 and the growing number of enrollment is prevalent.\n\n</string>
    <string name="eed2_ov"><![CDATA[This programme provides knowledge and hands-on skills for designing, installing, operating and enhancing sustainable energy systems that combine energy generation, distribution and utilization that caters to the demands of technologies in green energy and electrical power for application and services in building, industry and transportation. The student will acquire the skills in installation, testing & commissioning, and maintenance to ensure system safety, reliability and efficiency for renewable energy technologies, particularly, solar and wind power, which are the fastest growing sources of electricity besides geothermal and biomass systems. The requirements for certifying the distributed renewable energy systems will also be emphasized to ensure that the graduate is prepared for system installer certification which is require by the Sustainable Energy Development Authority (SEDA).]]></string>
    <string name="eed2_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Computer & Programming\n• Electrical Principles\n• German Language 1\n• Pre-Calculus\n• Engineering Science\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Technical Drawing & CAD\n\nSemester 2\n• Electronics\n• Digital Systems\n• Technical English 1\n• German Language 2\n• Electronics Workshop\n• Calculus\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban/ Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi 1\n\nSemester 3\n• Sensor & Transducer\n• Electrical Machines & Control\n• Technical English 2\n• Electrical Installation\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah/ Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n• Community Services\n• Microcontroller\n• Sustainable Energy Technology & System\n• Photovoltaic Principles & Materials\n\nSemester 4\n• Power Electronics & Modern Drive Technology\n• SPD Project Proposal\n• Programmable Logic Controllers\n• Electrical Devices\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• Hydro & Wind Energy System\n• Solar System Design & Application\n• Control Systems Application\n• Industrial Management\n\nSemester 5\n• Power Distribution System\n• SPD Final Project\n• Biomass Energy\n• Field Technology\n• Power Management & Analysis\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="eed2_path"><![CDATA[1. Photovoltaic Project Engineer\n2. Energy Management Manager\n3. Instrument & Power Plant Engineer\n4. Electrical Engineer\n5. Environmental Consultant\n6. R&D Engineer\n7. Sustainable Energy Technologist\n8. Renewable Energy Power Designer\n9. Renewable Energy System Integrator\n10.Solar Fabricator / Electrician]]></string>
    <string name="eed3_ov">Equips students with a profound knowledge and skills of electronic circuits and systems knowledge of telecommunications and computer controlled systems needed to meet the 21 st century industrial demands . The student will be able to design and build electronic and computer based systems and thus, preparing them for work in the high-tech industry. Students will acquire more in-depth knowledge and practical application of microprocessor, interface design, micro controller systems, local area network, radio frequency (RF), telecommunication system, data communications system and network administration. In addition, the programme also integrates communicative and thinking skills, project management, entrepreneurship, learning and interpersonal skills so that the students are prepared to face the rapid changes of IT technology.</string>
    <string name="eed3_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Computer & Programming\n• Electrical Principles\n• German Language 1\n• Pre-Calculus\n• Engineering Science\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Technical Drawing & CAD\n\nSemester 2\n• Electronics\n• Digital Systems\n• Technical English 1\n• German Language 2\n• Calculus\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban/ Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi 1\n• Data Management\n\nSemester 3\n• Electrical Control Systems\n• Electronic Circuit Analysis\n• Technical English 2\n• Electronics Workshop\n• Microprocessor\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah/ Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n• Community Services\n• Control Systems Application\n\nSemester 4\n• Network Design & Administration\n• Communication Principles\n• Microelectromechanical Systems\n• EIT Project Proposal\n• Industrial Management\n• Microcontroller\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• Programming in Visual Basic\n• FPGA & Applications\n\nSemester 5\n• Data Communication Systems\n• Broadband Technology\n• EIT Final Technology\n• Programming in JAVA\n• Computer Interfacing Technology\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="eed3_path">1. IT Assistant\n2. System Programmer/Analyst/Management\n3. Telecommunication Technologist\n4. Electronics Support Specialist\n5. Technical Support Specialist</string>
    <string name="eed4_ov">Provides students with sound theoretical and practical training in the operation and maintenance of automated process control and measurement systems to maintain a consistent product output. It is the art and science of measurement and control of process variables within a production, laboratory, or manufacturing area in the instance of typical process variables namely temperature, pressure, level and flow of industrial reactors may be controlled.</string>
    <string name="eed4_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Computer & Programming\n• Electrical Principles\n• German Language 1\n• Pre-Calculus\n• Engineering Science\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Technical Drawing & CAD\n\nSemester 2\n• Electronics\n• Digital Systems\n• Technical English 1\n• German Language 2\n• Electronics Workshop\n• Calculus\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban / Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi\n\nSemester 3\n• Sensor & Transducer\n• Electrical Machines & Control\n• Technical English 2\n• Data Acquisition Technology\n• Pneumatics & Hydraulics Technology\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah/ Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n• Community Services\n• Control Systems Application\n\nSemester 4\n• Programmable Logic Controllers\n• Electrical Installation\n• PIC Project Proposal\n• Process Measurement Technology\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• Process Technology System\n• Process Control Instrumentation\n• Industrial Management\n\nSemester 5\n• Power Electronics & Modern Drive Technology\n• PIC Final Project\n• Instrument Calibration & Maintenance\n• Basic Metal Work & Welding\n• Distributed Control System & Applications\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="eed4_path"><![CDATA[1. Field Assistant Engineer\n2. Control & Instrumentation Technologist\n3. Service Assistant Engineer\n4. Process Assistant Engineer]]></string>
    <string name="eed5_ov">Referred to as modern automotive technology and also commonly known as Automotive Electronic. Autotronics is the combination of automobile and electronics while hybrid refers to technology that uses two or more distinct power sources to move the vehicle. It deals with computer controlled motor vehicle systems such as Engine Control Unit (ECU-airbag, engine, ABS) , engine management , electronic transmission, GPS-based navigation system, stability management system, instrument ation, infotainment, etc.</string>
    <string name="eed5_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Basic Metal Work & Welding\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Electrical Principles\n• Health, Safety & Environment\n• Engineering Science\n• German Language 1\n• Computer Aided Design in Mechanical & Electrical\n• Pre-Calculus\n\nSemester 2\n• Calculus\n• Electronics\n• Technical English 1\n• German Language 2\n• Engine Structure\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban / Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi 1\n• Pneumatics & Hydraulics Technology\n\nSemester 3\n• Automotive Control Systems\n• Automotive Electrical Systems\n• Automotive Sensor & Actuator\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah/ Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n• Community Service\n• Engine Performance\n• Technical English 2\n• Vehicle Air Conditioning System\n\nSemester 4\n• AHS Project Proposal\n• Auxiliary System\n• Engine Management System\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• Hybrid Technology\n• Automotive Communication System\n• Transmission Systems\n• Industrial Management\n\nSemester 5\n• AHS Final Project\n• Alternative Energy Sources & Storage Devices\n• Automotive Troubleshooting & Maintenance\n• Electric Vehicle\n• Engineering Ethics\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="eed5_path"><![CDATA[1. Autotronics Specialist\n2. Production Assistant Technician\n3. Autotronics Assistant Engineer\n4. Research & Development Executive]]></string>
    <string name="cid1_ov">Designed to develop the competencies required in the software development process that involves the synchronized application of a broad spectrum of defect prevention and detection strategies in order to reduce software development risks, time, and costs.</string>
    <string name="cid1_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Discrete Mathematics\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• German Language 1\n• IT Essentials\n• Computer Ethics & Values\n• Basic of Software Engineering\n• Operating Systems\n\nSemester 2\n• English for Professional Purposes 1\n• German Language 2\n• Networking Fundamentals\n• Basic of Programming\n• Basic of Software Testing\n• Software Modelling & Requirements Engineering\n• Calculus & Algebra\n\nSemester 3\n• English for Professional Purposes 2\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban /\n   Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi 1\n• Dinamika Islam di Malaysia /\n   Etika & Moral Masyarakat Malaysia\n• Co-Curricular Activities & Community Services\n• Database Management System\n• Data Structure & Algorithm\n• Secured Object Oriented Programming\n\nSemester 4\n• Human Computer Interaction\n• SET Project Proposal\n• IT Project Management\n• Web Programming\n• Test Automation & Configuration\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• IoT Application & Software\n\nSemester 5\n• SET Final Project\n• Android Programming\n• Quality Assurance & Control\n• Artificial Intelligence in Modern Computing\n• Advanced Web Programming\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="cid1_path">Software\n– Tester\n– System Analysis\n– Quality Assurance Engineer\n– Assistant Developer\n– Application Mobile Developer</string>
    <string name="cid2_ov">To develop the competencies required in the security of overall network architecture which includes design and write computer programs, use and maintain databases, configure and integrate various network security tools and install and secure computer networks. It emphasizes on the security of overall network architecture, configuration and integration of various network security tools, which includes open source the proprietary software.</string>
    <string name="cid2_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• IT Essential\n• Cyber Security Technology & Ethics\n• Basic of Programming\n• German Language 1\n• Discrete Mathematics\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Network Fundamental\n\nSemester 2\n• Database Management System\n• English for Professional Purposes 1\n• German Language 2\n• Routing & Switching Essentials\n• Calculus & Algebra\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban\n• Bahasa Kebangsaan A*\n• Secured Object Oriented Programming\n\nSemester 3\n• Network Programming\n• Operating Systems Administration\n• English for Professional Purposes 2\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah/\n   Integrity and Anti Corruption Course\n• Community Service\n• Scaling Network\n• Web Programming\n\nSemester 4\n• IT Project Management\n• Wireless Network & Security\n• Penetration Testing\n• Intrusion Detection & Prevention Systems\n• CBS Project Proposal\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• Securing Network\n\nSemester 5\n• Digital Forensics & Incident Response\n• Cryptography\n• Internet of Things\n• CBS Final Project\n• Network Management & Monitoring Systems\n• Mobile Application Development\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="cid2_path">1. Cybersecurity Analyst\n2. Security Engineer / Architect\n3. Penetration Testing\n4. Security Consultant\n5. Ethical Hacker</string>
    <string name="cid3_ov">Diploma programme that familiarizes students with overall process of producing digital work art, particularly in 2D and 3D. It emphasizes on nurturing creative young minds of Malaysian youth to the workflow of media during pre-production stage, production and post-production stages, including sketching, drawing, modelling, texturing, animating and rendering of 2D and 3D animation work piece. Students will be actively exposed in creative design and animation, with state-of-the-art software and hardware for producing short multimedia animation, together with narration using industry-standard recording studio for sound editing and mixing. The programme also nurtures the students’ awareness as digital entrepreneurs, promotes thinking and problem-solving skills, and life-long learning.</string>
    <string name="cid3_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Creativity and Innovation\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• German Language 1\n• Multimedia in Concept\n• Storyboard Visualization\n• Computer & Programming\n• Computer Ethics & Values\n• Sketching & Drawing\n\nSemester 2\n• English for Professional Purposes 1\n• German Language 2\n• Multimedia OOP\n• Digital Imaging\n• Multimedia Instructional Design\n• Graphic Design & Composition\n• Artificial Intelligence in Multimedia Technologies\n• Bahasa Kebangsaan A*\n\nSemester 3\n• English for Professional Purposes 2\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban / Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi 1\n• Community Services\n• Web Programming with HTML\n• Database Management System\n• 2D Animation\n• Multimedia Authoring\n\nSemester 4\n• Digital Video & Audio\n• Human Computer Interaction\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• 3D Animation\n• CRM Project Proposal\n\nSemester 5\n• CRM Final Project\n• Web Programming with PHP• \nMobile Application Development\n• Multimedia Project Management\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="cid3_path"><![CDATA[1. Creative Media Editor\n2. Web Designer\n3. Creative Designer\n4. 2D / 3D Animator\n5. Photographer & Videographer\n6. Mobile Apps Developer]]></string>
    <string name="mecha1_ov"><![CDATA["Focused on three main manufacturing skills based on Tool and Die, sheet metal and Plastic Engineering where the participant/student will utilize various skills such as design in 2D & 3D design, state of the art engineering analysis, modern fabrication and manufacturing, maintenances and overall production. The students will use their creativity to develop various designs based on current or future consumers-based product which require them to be detail oriented and have an interest in mechanical processes. Computer-aided design (CAD) software and Computer-aided manufacturing (CAM) will be utilized to make sure the participant/student are capable to meet Malaysia and others nations standards in their pursuits in mechanical engineering. "]]></string>
    <string name="mecha1_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Machine Tool Operation\n• Pre-Calculus\n• Manufacturing Process\n• Basic Cutting Process\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Engineering Metrology\n• Engineering Drawing\n• Electrical Technology\n\nSemester 2\n• Technical English 1\n• Workshop Practice\n• Calculus\n• Engineering Science\n• Engineering Materials\n• Geometrical Dimensioning & Tolerancing\n• Computer Aided Design\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah / Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n\nSemester 3\n• CAD CAM 2 & 3 Axis\n• CNC Milling & Turning Technology\n• Technical English 2\n• German Language 1\n• Jigs & Fixtures Manufacturing\n• Jigs & Fixtures Design\n• Engineering Mechanics\n• Further Calculus*\n• Community Services\n\nSemester 4\n• CAD CAM 4 & 5 Axis\n• Reverse Engineering\n• CNC Milling Multi Axis & Programming\n• CNC Grinding\n• CNC Turning Multi Axis & Programming\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• German Language 2\n• Industrial Management\n• Welding\n• CPT Project Proposal\n\nSemester 5\n• EDM Technology\n• Machine Tool Maintenance\n• Pneumatics & Hydraulics\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban / Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi 1\n• Bahasa Kebangsaan A*\n• CPT Final Project\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="mecha1_path">1. Production Engineer\n2. Mould and Die Design Engineer\n3. Machinist Expert\n4. Quality Assurance Engineer\n5. Technical Trainer or Consultant\n6. Sales Engineer\n7. Production Supervisor\n8. Expert Technician</string>
    <string name="mecha2_ov"><![CDATA[The industrial design programme prepares students to be creative, practical, aesthetics-focused, collaborative problem-solver, and to conduct the design process from project brief to design implementation. Students not only create and develop design work but each creation of design is optimized in its function, value and appearance. Industrial Design adapts into the changing and developing technology by supporting the manufacturing and engineering industries in areas like digital design, 3D modeling, prototyping & manufacturing processes. The students is expected to acquire presentations, problem-solving, communication, documentation, and organizational skills during the phases of the design process through industry collaborations and studio projects.]]></string>
    <string name="mecha2_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Design History\n• Engineering Drawing\n• Engineering Methodology\n• Basic Cutting Process\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Machine Tool Operation\n• Manufacturing Processes\n• Pre-Calculus\n\nSemester 2\n• Design Studio 1 (Sketching)\n• Computer Aided Design\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah / Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n• Engineering Materials\n• Engineering Science\n• Workshop Practice\n• Technical English 1\n• Calculus\n\nSemester 3\n• Design Project 1\n• Form Study 1\n• Creativity & Innovation\n• Engineering Mechanics\n• Community Services\n• Technical English 2\n• German Language 1\n• Ergonomics\n• Electrical Technology\n\nSemester 4\n• Design Project 2\n• Design Studio 2 (Sketching)\n• Digital Design & Styling 1\n• Form 2\n• German Language 2\n• IDE Project Proposal\n• Industrial Management\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n\nSemester 5\n• Design Project 3\n• Digital Design & Styling 2\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban / Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi\n• IDE Final Project\n• Product Development & Marketing\n• Prototype Technology & Applications\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="mecha2_path"><![CDATA[1. Industrial Design Projects – Product Design , Automotive Design , Furniture Design\n2. Digital Design & Styling\n3. 3D Modeling\n4. 3D Visualization\n5. Prototype Technology & Applications]]></string>
    <string name="mecha3_ov">Focuses on the knowledge and skills aspects in the field of inspection and quality engineering required by the industry. The program aims to produce skilled, competitive, scientifically-minded, creative, competent, and capable human resources in solving quality issues and problems at a workplace. The program develop students with the key skills in the field of quality such as aspects of planning, implementation, checking and corrective action on the problems faced by the industry in achieving their targets. Students are exposed to the standard systems as well as continuous improvement methods based on Total Quality Management (TQM).</string>
    <string name="mecha3_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Machine Tool Operation\n• Pre-Calculus\n• Basic Cutting Process\n• Manufacturing Processes\n• Total Quality Management\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Engineering Metrology\n• Engineering Drawing\n\nSemester 2\n• Technical English 1\n• Quality Tools\n• Calculus\n• Engineering Science\n• Engineering Materials\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah / Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n• Computer Aided Design\n\nSemester 3\n• CNC Milling & Turning Technology\n• Electrical & Electronics for Industry\n• Technical English 2\n• German Language 1\n• Further Calculus\n• Community Services\n• Ergonomics in Industry\n• Continuous Improvement Technique\n• Lean Manufacturing\n\nSemester 4\n• German Language 2\n• Six Sigma Management System\n• Industrial Management\n• Quality Standard & Auditing\n• Mechanical Instrument Calibration\n• GD&T Inspection\n• IQM Project Proposal\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n\nSemester 5\n• Operational Safety, Health & Enviroment\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban / Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi\n• Inspection and Testing\n• IQM Final Project\n• Instrument Calibration & Maintenance\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="mecha3_path">1. QA Assistant Engineer\n2. Quality:\n   – Assurance Supervisor\n   – Auditor\n   – Trainer\n   – Management System (QMS) Coordinator\n3. QA/QC Technician\n4. Quality Control\n   – Assistant Engineer\n   – Inspector\n5. Audit Assistant Executive\n6. Assistant Industrial Engineer\n7. Measuring Technician\n8. Process Improvement Coordinator</string>
    <string name="mecha4_ov">Focuses on product design concepts, presentation of new product ideas and advanced manufacturing applications for production. The programme provides a thorough understanding of design principles, manufacturing processes, and manufacturing technologies for which the activities involve the entire product lifecycle, from the identification of a market opportunity or requirements, through design, testing and manufacture. After the attainment of the technical foundation, the core competencies in the programme will be facilitated by a wide range of technology disciplines namely rapid prototyping, ergonomics and design, product design for manufacturing, and advanced manufacturing.</string>
    <string name="mecha4_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Machine Tool Operation\n• Pre-Calculus\n• Manufacturing Processes\n• Basic Cutting Process\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Engineering Metrology\n• Engineering Drawing\n\nSemester 2\n• Technical English 1\n• Workshop Practice\n• Calculus\n• Engineering Science\n• Engineering Materials\n• Geometrical Dimensioning & Tolerancing\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah / Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n• Computer Aided Design\n\nSemester 3\n• Design Conceptualization & Ideation\n• Creativity & Innovation\n• Model Making Techniques\n• Electrical Technology\n• Technical English 2\n• German Language 1\n• Engineering Mechanics\n• Further Calculus*\n• Plastic Product Design & Tooling\n• Community Service\n\nSemester 4\n• Design for Manufacturing & Assembly\n• Ergonomics\n• Digital Design & Styling\n• German Language 2\n• Industrial Management\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• Prototype Technology & Application\n• Welding\n• PDM Project Proposal\n• Sheet Metal Design & Tooling\n\nSemester 5\n• CNC Programming & CAD CAM\n• Reverse Engineering\n• Engineering Analysis\n• Pneumatics & Hydraulics\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban / Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi 1\n• Product Development & Marketing\n• Bahasa Kebangsaan A*\n• PDM Final Project\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="mecha4_path">1. Product Designer\n2. CAD Application Assistant Engineer\n3. Product and Realibility Assistant Engineer\n4. Quality Assurance Executive</string>
    <string name="mecha5_ov"><![CDATA[The Diploma in CNC Precision Technology (CPT) program emphasizes fundamental knowledge and skills in Computer Numerical Control (CNC) precision machining technologies and processes. The program covers various applications of CNC precision machining, including CNC milling 2 & 3 axis, CNC milling 5 axis, CNC turning, and CNC grinding, as well as the concept of CNC machining and machine setup.]]></string>
    <string name="mecha5_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Machine Tool Operation\n• Pre-Calculus\n• Manufacturing Processes\n• Basic Cutting Process\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Engineering Metrology\n• Engineering Drawing\n• Electrical Technology\n\nSemester 2\n• Technical English 1\n• Workshop Practice\n• Calculus\n• Engineering Science\n• Engineering Materials\n• Geometrical Dimensioning & Tolerancing\n• Computer Aided Design\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah / Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n\nSemester 3\n• CAD CAM 2 & 3 Axis\n• CNC Milling & Turning Technology\n• Technical English 2\n• German Language 1\n• Jigs & Fixtures Manufacturing\n• Jigs & Fixtures Design\n• Engineering Mechanics\n• Further Calculus*\n• Community Service\n\nSemester 4\n• CAD CAM 4 & 5 Axis\n• Reverse Engineering\n• CNC Milling Multi Axis & Programming\n• CNC Grinding\n• CNC Turning Multi Axis & Programming\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• German Language 2\n• Industrial Management\n• Welding\n• CPT Project Proposal\n\nSemester 5\n• EDM Technology\n• Machine Tool Maintenance\n• Pneumatics & Hydraulics\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban / Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi 1\n• Bahasa Kebangsaan A*\n• CPT Final Project\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="mecha5_path"><![CDATA[1. CNC\n   – Milling Machinist\n   – Milling Programmer\n   – Turning Machinist\n   – Programmer Programmer\n   – Trainer\n   – Technician\n2. CAM Programmer\n3. CAD Draftsman\n4. Jig & Fixture Designer\n5. Assistant\n   – Manager\n   – Application Engineer\n   – Production Engineer\n6. Production Executive]]></string>
    <string name="mecha6_ov">Driven by a number of factors, including the migration from manual to CNC machine tools, higher production rates and higher quality requirements in which reducing machine tool downtime and assuring quality have become increasingly important as the demand for higher production rates and closer tolerance continue to grow. Other that learning about how each part of the machine functions in relation to the overall machine process, the students will be equipped to develop and conduct a preventive maintenance programmes that will maximize the machine tool performance.</string>
    <string name="mecha6_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Electrical Technology\n• Machine Tool Operation\n• Pre-Calculus\n• Basic Cutting Process\n• Manufacturing Process\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Engineering Metrology\n• Engineering Drawing\n\nSemester 2\n• Technical English 1\n• Workshop Practice\n• Calculus\n• Engineering Science\n• Engineering Materials\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah/ Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n• Geometrical Dimensioning & Tolerancing\n\nSemester 3\n• Community Service\n• Engineering Mechanics\n• Technical English 2\n• German Language\n• Maintenance Fundamentals\n• Motion & Systems Control\n• Pneumatic & Hydraulics System Maintenance\n• Programmable Logic Controllers\n• Further Calculus*\n\nSemester 4\n• CNC Operation\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n• German Language 2\n• Industrial Management\n• Machine Electrical Faults & Diagnosis\n• Machine Electrical Design & Operation\n• Machine Tolerances & Calibration\n• MTM Project Proposal\n\nSemester 5\n• Occupational Safety, Health & Environment\n• Machine Repair & Retrofit\n• MTM Final Project\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban/ Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi 1\n• Bahasa Kebangsaan A*\n• Total Productive Maintenance\n• Welding\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="mecha6_path">1. Field Service Machine Maintenance\n2. Assistance Engineer\n3. Machine\n   – Designer and Retrofitting (Executive)\n   – Designer\n   – Expert\n   – Associate\n   – Automation Specialist\n4. Maintenance\n   – Manager (Executive)\n   – Engineer\n   – Planner Scheduler\n   – Mechanic\n   – Administrative Specialist\n5. Project Assistant Engineer (Executive)\n6. Engineering Supervisor (Executive)\n7. Operation Engineer\n8. Precision Machine Tool Mechanic\n9. Industrial Maintenance Technician Instructor</string>
    <string name="mecha7_ov">Manufacturing System (MFS) is a program that emphasizes the interrelationships between manufacturing equipment, processes and controls, and their integration into production factories. The combination of technological knowledge of high-tech production systems and knowledge of production processes is essential for manufacturing organizations to be efficient, innovative and sustainable in the increasingly competitive markets.</string>
    <string name="mecha7_subj"><![CDATA[Semester 1\n• Machine Tool Operation\n• Pre-Calculus\n• Manufacturing Process\n• Basic Cutting Process\n• Effective Communication Skills\n• Engineering Metrology\n• Engineering Drawing\n\nSemester 2\n• Technical English 1\n• Workshop Practice\n• Calculus\n• Engineering Science\n• Engineering Materials\n• Geometrical Dimensioning & Tolerancing\n• Computer Aided Design\n• Kursus Integriti dan Antirasuah/ Integrity and Anti-Corruption Course\n\nSemester 3\n• CNC Programming & CAD CAM\n• Electrical Technology\n• Technical English 2\n• German Language 1\n• Further Calculus*\n• Community Service\n• Automated Manufacturing\n• Flexible Manufacturing System\n• Statics & Dynamics\n\nSemester 4\n• German Language 2\n• Pneumatics & Hydraulics\n• Industrial Management\n• Welding\n• Electro-Mechanics\n• Computer Integrated Manufacturing System (CIMS)\n• Machine Elements Design & Operation\n• MSD Project Proposal\n• Digital Entrepreneurship\n\nSemester 5\n• Engineering Analysis\n• Robust Industrial Design\n• Statistical Process Control\n• Penghayatan Etika dan Peradaban/ Bahasa Melayu Komunikasi\n• Bahasa Kebangsaan A*\n• Production Planning Control\n• MSD Final Project\n\nSemester 6\n• Industrial Training]]></string>
    <string name="mecha7_path">1. Manufacturing Assistant Engineer\n2. Industrial Assistant Engineer\n3. Automation Technical Assistant\n4. Production Assistant Engineer / Technical Supervisor</string>
    <string name="eed_desc">Focuses on electrical principles, circuits, and power systems with strong hands-on training for industry needs.</string>
    <string name="mecha_desc">Provides practical and theoretical training in mechanics, design, and manufacturing using modern engineering tools.</string>
    <string name="cid_desc">Covers computing fundamentals, software skills, networking, and IT concepts to prepare students for digital-tech careers.</string>
    <string name="degree_desc">Degree Programme in Collaboration with Universiti Teknikal Malaysia Melaka (UTeM)</string>
    <string name="gapp_desc">Pathway for German university entrance and preparatory modules</string>
    <string name="gufp_desc">Foundation programme to prepare for undergraduate studies</string>
</resources>